자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀.
(http://club.nate.com/clubcsi)
자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀
거짓말하지 마. 나이트에서
춤출 때마다 입술로 그렇게 하잖아
Liar. Everytime you're on the danceing
floor, you do that with your lips.
- 안 그래
- 아냐, 그래 / 너도 알지
- I do not.
- Yeah, you do. / You know it.
여섯 번째
Number six. Oh...
섹스해 본 곳 중에
가장 깨는 장소는?
What's the craziest place
you've ever done it?
어, 꼭 고르라면
사장 책상 위에서였지
Uh, if I had to choose,
it would be on my boss's desk.
내가 미쳐
Oh, please.
얘들아, 저 비행기 좀 봐
Hey, look at that plane.
이야, 상당히 낮게 나네
Oh, wow.
It's pretty low, isn't it?
우리 쪽으로 방향을
돌리는 거 같은데
And it looks like it's truning toward us.
우리 가슴 보여 주자
Oh, let's flash him.
그래, 보여 줘
Yeah. Flash him.
미치려고 할 거야
They're gonna freak.
저기, 무슨 문제 있는 거 아냐?
Hey is...is that thing in trouble?
우리 쪽으로
곧바로 오는 거 같은데
It looks like it's coming straight at us.
그럴 리가
No.
그런 거야?
Is it?
불타고 있어!
야, 고개 숙여!
It's on fire.
Dude, swerve...
괜찮아요?
Are you okay?
예, 괜찮아요
I am.
그렇지만 부조종사는
도움이 필요할 거 같네요
I think my copilot needs
some help, though.
예, 뭐든 말씀하세요
Sure, yeah.
Anything.
그거 수갑이에요?
Are those handcuffs?
오, 세상에
Oh, my God!
안 돼. 그러지 마
제발 살려 줘
Don't, don't.
Please, don't.
그럼 나한테 보답을 해야지
Make it worth my while.
네가 하라는 대로 다할게
I'll do anything you say.
이제야 그 말을 하는군
Oh, you say that now.
차에 타
Get in the car.
부조종사도 죽었나, 프랭크?
Copilot dead, too, Frank?
그래. 비행기 안에 있어
Yeah, he's inside.
연방 보안관의 총을 가져갔어
He's got the Marshal's gun.
조종사가 조난 신호를 보냈더군
Pilot radioed a Mayday.
관제탑에서는 뭐라고 하는지
알아듣지 못했대
Controller couldn't understand
what he was saying.
프랭크, 누군가가 고의로
이 비행기를 추락시켰네
Frank, this plane was sabotaged.
몇 km 떨어진 곳에서부터
연기를 봤다는 목격자들이 있어
Witnesses saw smoke a mile away.
이건 서장님이 책임져야 할 거야
This is gonna fall on the Chief.
리디아 존슨의 시체를
찾기 위해서 헨리 데리어스를
He's the one who approved
Henry Darius flying down to
마이애미로 이송하는 걸
허락한 사람이니까
Miami to find the body
of Lydia Johnson.
내 바람과는 반대로 말이지
Against my wishes.
애들 부모 말로는, 애들이
노란색 컨버터블 머스탱을 몰고 나갔대
Kids' parents say, they, uh,
drove a yellow convertible Mustang.
내가 수배를 내릴게
I'll put out a broadcast.
데리어스와 신원 미상의
죄수를 찾으라고
Darius and a convict to be named later.
무장한 데다 위험하기까지 한
놈들이야, 프랭크
Armed and dangerous, Frank.
딕테이션
이근양(kylee322@nate.com)
싱크편집
송미혜(smh8119@nate.com)
한글번역
박진원(azy0070@lycos.co.kr)
데이비드 카루소(호레이시오 케인 役)
CSI 레벨 3(반장), 전문분야 : 방화, 폭발
에밀리 프록터(캘리 뒤케인 役)
CSI 레벨 2, 전문분야 : 탄도학, 스페인어
애덤 로드리게즈(에릭 델코 役)
CSI 레벨 1, 전문분야 : 지문, 수중탐사, 스페인어
콴디 알렉산더(알렉스 우즈 役)
검시관, 전문분야 : 법의학
조나단 토고(라이언 울프 役)
CSI 레벨 1
CSI: Miami
4x07 Felony Flight
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2005/11/07
바닥 판이 뜯겨 나갔어
Floor panel's gone.
여기 있는 전선은 다
전기 스위치 어셈블리야
All these wires are the
electrical switch assembly.
저 관에 있는
단열재가 뜯겨져 나갔어
Insulations ripped off that pipe.
냉각제가 지나가는 관 같아
Looks like a coolant duct.
그러니까 누군가가 구멍을 낸 거네
So, somebody punctured it.
그래. 구멍이 나면서
뜨거운 기체가 분출되었을 테니까...
Yeah,that puncture
released hot gas, so I bet....
틀림없이 손에 화상을 입었을 거야
I bet our guy has burns on his hands.
저기 있는 관 말이야
저 안에는 뜨거운 압축 공기가 지나가
That pipe right there..
that pipe contains hot bleed air.
공기를 엔진 밖으로 내보내는 거지
Keeps it away from the engines.
관에 구멍이 나서
공기가 조금씩 새어 나오니까
When he punctured the pipe,
it caused a slow leak,
엔진의 온도가 올라갔겠네
and that raised the
temperature of the engine.
그래서 비상 착륙을
할 수밖에 없었던 거야
And caused an emergency landing.
- 이제 블랙박스를 찾으러 가자
- 그래
Come on. Let's look
for the black box. / Right.
- 뉴욕에 알렸어
- 고맙네
- Notified New York.
- Appreciate it.
테일러 반장이 안부를 전하고
공조 수사를 하겠대
Detective Taylor sends his regards,
offers his services.
맥은 훌륭한 수사관이지
Mac's a good man.
자네가 그렇게 말할 줄 알았네
이쪽으로 오라고 할게
I figured you'd say that.
I'll tell him to come down.
아티카 교도소에서 데리어스와 관계가
있었던 모든 사람의 정보가 필요해
We need everybody that Darius
dealt with at Attica, okay?
그렇게 전하지
I'll tell him.
고맙네
Thank you.
애가 차 밖으로 나올 때까지
기다렸어요
I waited till the kid got out of the car.
6, 7살 정도였죠
He was about six, seven years old.
존슨 부인의 아들 말이군
그 후에 어떻게 했어?
Mrs. Johnson's son.
What did you do after that?
차에 타서 존슨 부인의
머리에 총을 겨눴어요
I got in the car and held
a gun to her head.
소리 지르면
머리를 날려 버릴 거야
Scream and I'll blow you head off.
그 여자가 반항하고 소리를 질러서
제가 조치를 취했죠
She was fighting, screaming,
so I took care of it.
어떻게 조치했다는 거야?
Took care of how?
쏴 버렸죠
Shot her.
그러니까 찍소리도 못하더군요
She didn't make a peep after that.
다시 한 번 묻지
존슨 부인의 시체를 어디에 묻었어?
I'm gonna ask you again.
Where did you bury her body?
이젠 그보다 더 깊게 파야 할 겁니다
Now, you dig deeper than that.
그래서야 어디 존슨 부인의
시체를 찾으려고 나를
And there's no reason for
you to take me all the way from
뉴욕에서 마이애미까지
보낼 이유가 없지 않겠어요?
New York to Miami to show
you her body, is there?
뭔가 더 불어야 마이애미 경찰에서
널 비행기에 태울 거야
Miami-Dade's not putting you
on a plane without something.
진주 롤렉스 시계를 차고 있었어요
She had on a pearl Rolex.
가짜 진주 롤렉스 시계요
A fake pearl Rolex.
존슨 씨
Mr. Johnson.
반장님, 전 플로리다에서 가장 큰
라디오 방송국을 가지고 있습니다
Lieutenant, I own the largest
conglomerate of radio stations in Florida,
그러니 당연히 그 뉴스를 들었죠
so of course I heard news
그렇지만 전화 주신 건
감사드립니다
but I would have
appreciated a phone call.
선생님, 이해합니다. 그런 식으로
소식을 들으시게 해서 죄송합니다
Sir, I understnad, and I'm sorry
you had to find out like this.
그러니까 제 아내를 죽인
놈을 잡아들여 놓고는
So, you guys found the
guy who killed my wife,
도망가게 놔뒀다는 건가요?
and you let him get away?
존슨 씨, 데리어스가 부인을
죽이지 않았을 수도 있습니다
Mr. Johnson. It's possible that
Darius did not kill your wife.
그럼 왜 뉴욕 감옥에서 이리로
데려온 겁니까?
Then why did you bring him down
here from a New York prison?
부인이 매장되어 있는 곳을
알아내기 위해서였습니다
To provide us with information
about where she's buried.
일 년 전에도 말했지만 전 아직도 리디아가
살아 있을 거란 희망을 갖고 있어요
I said it a year ago, and I'm still
holding out hope that Lydia's alive.
이해합니다만 부인의 차에서
발견한 피의 양으로 볼 때
I understand, but with the amount
of blood that we recovered from
그럴 가능성은 거의 없을 것 같습니다
her vehicle, I think that's unlikely.
제 아들은 아직도 엄마가
집에 돌아오기를 기다리고 있어요
My son, still waits for his
mother to come home.
현관에 불도 못 끄게 해요
He won't let me turn
out the porch light.
뭔가 확실한 결론이 난다면
도움이 될 것 같군요
If we could have some closure, it'd help.
존슨 씨, 제 모든 능력을 다해서
Mr. Johnson,
I am going to do everything
부인을 찾을 겁니다. 아셨죠?
in my power to find your wife, okay?
감사합니다
Thank you.
뭘 찾아내야 하죠?
What are we looking for?
나도 아직 잘 모르겠어
I don't know yet.
눈이 죽어 있어
Dead eyes.
가장 무서운 범죄자 유형이지
It's scariest kind of criminal.
호버만 씨가 날 도와줬어요
Mr. Hoberman helped me.
이젠 그보다
더 깊게 파야 할 겁니다
Now, you dig deeper than that...
재밌네 / 뭐가요?
Interesting. / What?
호버만 씨가 날 도와줬어요
Mr. Hoberman helped me.
데리어스에 관한
기록을 읽어 봤어?
Did you look into the files on Darius?
강력반에서 봤다더라고요
Homicide did.
여기하고 뉴욕에 있는
사건 기록들을 봤는데
They looked at the files
here and in New York,
어디에도 호버만에 대한
언급은 없었대요
but there isn't mentioned of a Hoberman.
이젠, 그보다 더 깊게...
Now, you dig deeper...
더 깊게 파라...
우릴 가지고 놀고 있어
Dig deeper.
He's playing with us.
어떤 식으로요?
He's playing how?
나도 몰라
I don't know.
존슨 부인이 사라진 날을 전후해서 나온
신문을 샅샅이 찾아보자
Let's pull up all the newspapers
surrounding the day
Mrs. Johnson went missing.
콜린스 가에 새로 지을
콘도에 대한 광고를 찾았어
Got an ad here for new
condos on Collins.
"2006년 겨울에
착공을 시작합니다"
"Digging begins winter of '06."
호버만은 없네
No Hoberman.
세인트오거스틴 시에서 있었던
고고학 발굴에 대한 기사를 찾았어요
I go an archeological
dig up in St. Augustine.
호버만에 대한 언급은 있어?
Any mention of Hoberman?
없어요
No.
여기 호비 서핑 보드에 관한
광고가 하나 있네
Got an ad here for Hobie boards.
어쩌면 호버만이라는 단어는
암호일지도 몰라
Maybe it's a bastardization of Hoberman.
- 선배
- 그럴 수도 있잖아
- Calleigh.
- It could happen.
선배 / 왜?
Cal. / What?
부고란이에요. "앨버트 호버만
2004년 10월 31에 사망하다"
Obituaries. Albert Hoberman,
died October 31, 2004.
존슨 부인이 실종되기 전날이잖아
That's the day before
Lydia Johnson went missing.
그리고 11월 2일에 매장했어요
But he was interred, November 2.
존슨 부인이 실종된 다음날이죠
That was the day after she went missing.
"깊게 파다"
어느 공동묘지인지 나와 있어?
"Dig deep"
Does it say what cemetery?
예. 서프글라이드 가에 있는
몬테피오레 묘지예요
Yeah, Montefiore Acres, Surfglide Way.
영장이 필요하겠는데
We're gonna need a warrant.
그리고 중장비도요
And some heavy equipment.
나무 관이군
Coffin's wood.
여전히 새것 같네
Still looks new.
존슨 부인이 안에 있는지 살펴보죠
Let's see if Lydia Johnson's inside.
기록엔 호버만 씨가
According to the file, Mr. Hoberman
평온하게 자연사했다고 되어 있어
died peacefully of natural causes.
일치하는 것 같은데
Everything looks consistent.
- 존슨 부인은 없어
- 호버만 씨 아래에 없어요?
- No Lydia.
- She's not under him?
이 관 안에는 없어
Not in this casket.
호버만 씨뿐이야
He's in here alone.
여기 보세요
Guys.
삽이 있어요
It's a shovel.
관 아래에 있었네요
It was under the coffin.
"더 파라"라고 했죠
"Dig deeper"
시멘트로 둘러싸여 있어
That's surrounded by cement.
시멘트 벽은 장례식 전날에 만들지
Crypts are set the day before.
그러니 존슨 부인을 여기에
매장할 수는 없었겠죠
So, Lydia couldn't be buried here.
존슨 부인은 다른 곳에 매장됐겠지만
삽에 피가 묻어 있어요
Well, she had to be buried somewhere,
and there's blood on the shovel.
검사해 보면 틀림없이
존슨 부인 걸 거예요
Bet if we test it,
It's hers.
데리어스는 교활한 녀석이야
Your Darius is one tricky guy.
장례식 소식을 신문에서 보고
Looked in the paper for burials,
장례식 전에 나타나서
showed up before the ceremony,
이제 막 파 놓은 낯선 사람의
무덤에 삽을 넣어 놓고 갔어
put the shovel in a stranger's
freshly dug grave.
아무도 살펴볼 생각을
못하는 곳이죠
Where no one would ever think to look.
재밌는 건, 삽을 무덤에 묻는 바람에
You know, the funny thing is,
by buring the shovel in that crypt,
증거가 보존되었을지도
모른다는 거예요
he may have preserved the evidence.
에릭
Eric.
블랙박스는 어떻게 됐나?
The black box?
찾았는데 FBI가 갑자기
나타나서는 가져가 버렸어요
I got it, but the feds
swooped in and took it.
그렇지만 조종사
통신 기록은 받아왔어요
I did get the pilot's transcripts, though.
그래, 그거면 됐어
Okay, that's good enough.
조종사가 오파라카로 방향을 돌리고 있다고
마이애미 국제공항에 말했어요
He told Miami International he
was diverting to Opa-Locka.
아주 긴박한 목소리였어요
There was a lot of stress in his voice.
잠깐만...
Wait a second...
오파라카 공항으로 방향을 바꿨다고?
diverting to Opa-Locka Airport?
예. 그러곤 기계적인 문제로
몇 km를 남겨두고 비상 착륙했죠
Yeah, then mechanical problems
brought him down a couple
of miles short.. he crash landed.
어떻게 생각하세요?
What are you thinking?
누가 아직 데리어스를 기다리고
있을지도 모르겠군, 에릭
Sombody may still be
waiting for him, Eric.
예, 트립 형사님께 연락할게요
All right, I'll tell Tripp.
거기서 만나자고 전해 주게
Have him meet me there.
오지 않을 겁니다
He's not gonna make it, ma'am.
뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
헨리 데리어스 말입니다
Henry Darius.
데리어스는 나타나지 않을 겁니다
He's not gonna show.
누구를 말씀하시는지 모르겠군요
I don't know who you're talking about.
아티카 교도소에서 받은
데리어스의 펜팔 명단이 있어요
Ma'am, we have a list of
his pen pals from Attica.
빌어먹을 언론의 자유인가 뭔가 덕분에
죄수들이 인터넷을 자유롭게 돌아다니다
Prisoner stroll the Internet.
Freedom of speech b.s.
이런 저질들이 당신 같은
여자를 낚아채는 겁니다
And those lowlifes reel
in women like you.
연쇄 살인범과 사랑에
빠지는 여자들을 말이죠
Women that fall in love with serial killers.
헨리와 전 통하는 데가 많았어요
Henry and I did correspond.
헨리는 정말 친절하고
사려 깊고 상냥한 사람이죠
He's very nice, thoughtful, and caring,
머리도 정말 좋고요
exceptionally intelligent.
그래서 데리어스를
탈출시키려고 한 거군요
So you thought you'd
spring him from prison.
그놈이 비행기를 돌리면 당신이
별장으로 데려갈 생각으로 여기 온 거죠?
He diverts a plane, you're here to with
him away to your villa, is that right?
무슨 말을 하시는지
전혀 모르겠군요
I have no idea what you're talking about.
그럼 저 가방을 조사해 봐도
괜찮겠군요
Then you won't mind
us checking that bag.
2만 달러 정도 되는 거 같아
Looks like about 20 large.
제 거예요
It's mine.
부인, 제 생각엔
Ma'am, if I were to guess,
데리어스에게 줄 돈인 거 같군요
I would say that's expense
money for Mr. Darius.
증명해 보세요
You prove that.
전 하이비스커스 섬에 가 있을 테니
그리로 연락하세요
You can reach me on Hibiscus Island.
트립입니다
This is Tripp.
알았어
All right.
57번가와 플래글러 가 사이에서
아이들 차를 찾았대
Cops got the kids' car
inside 57th and Flagler.
남자 운전자 한 명이라는군
One male driver.
전자파를 사용하라고 해
내가 그리로 가겠네
Tell them to use the pulse.
I'll meet them there.
부인, 멀리 가지는 마십시오
Ma'am, don't leave town.
이제 그만하면 됐네
That's far enough, gentleman.
데리어스는 어디 있나, 켄?
Where's Darius, Ken?
전 모릅니다
I don't know.
누가 비행기를 추락시켰지?
자넨가, 데리어스인가?
Who brought the plane
down, you or him?
전 이 일에 끼어들고 싶지 않았어요
I didn't want any part of this
사기 혐의로 여기서 재판을
받게 돼 있었거든요
I was supposed to stand to trial
for fraud case down here.
난 그저 사무직 직원일 뿐이라고요
I'm strictly white collar.
자네였군. 팔에 있는 건
압축 공기로 인한 화상이야
So it was you.. that's a
gas burn on your arm.
데리어스가 절
풀어줄 거라고 했어요
Darius said he'd let me go.
오파라카에 도착하면 말이지
As soon as you got to Opa-Locka.
지금 화장실에 가
You should probably
go to the bathroom now.
시간을 잘못 계산했어요
너무 빨리 움직였던 거죠
Timed it wrong.
We fell short.
바지에 피가 묻은 게 보이는데, 켄
I notice that blood on your pants, Ken.
어디서 묻은 건가?
What's that from?
비행기 추락할 때요
The plane crash.
아냐, 그렇지 않아
둘이 무슨 짓을 한 거야?
No, it's not.
What did you guys do?
전 아무 짓도 안 했어요
그냥 도망쳤어요
I didn't do anything, I ran.
켄, 데리어스가
또 누구를 죽였나?
Ken...
Did Darius just kill someone?
누구를 죽였어?
Did he just kill someone?
어디에 내려 줬는지 당장 말해
I want a location right now.
마이애미 대학 캠퍼스
가장자리에 있는 건물에요
Miami U. building,
at the edge of campus.
쎄타 감마라던가 그랬어요
Theta Gamma something.
당신들은 몰라요
You don't understand.
그놈 눈을 보니
이미 늦었더라고요
Looked into the guy's eyes,
it's too late.
자네도 마찬가지야
For you, too.
그놈이 이제 진짜 신호탄을 날렸군
It's like real starting fire him off.
그래, 그렇군
Yes, it does.
데리어스 같은 놈이 스스로
그만둘 것 같나, 호레이시오?
You think guy like Darius
can stop his own, Horatio?
그 녀석은 우리가 잡을 때까지
멈추지 않을 거야
He's not gonna stop until
we make him stop.
삽에 있던 피는
존슨 부인 거였어요
So the blood on the shovle
matches Lydia Johnson.
그래. 그렇지만 데리어스가
존슨 부인을 파묻지는 않았어
Yes, but Darius did not bury Lydia.
그럼 어떻게 그런 특정한
정보를 알고 있는 거죠?
Then how'd he get specific information?
공범이 있었을까요, 아니면
교도소에서 도는 소문을 들었을까요?
Did he have a partner, did he hear
it through the prison grapevine?
이건 데리어스의 수법이 아냐
삽에 있던 흙은 어때? 도움이 되겠던가?
It's not his MO. How about the
soil on the shovel.. did it help?
어떻게 보시느냐에 따라 다르죠
이회토(泥灰土)였어요
Depends how you look at it...
it's marl soil.
이회토라, 여름 우기에
퇴적된 칼슘이군
Marl soil, calcium from the
summer wet season.
맞아요. 그건 존슨 부인이 데이드 카운티의
저지대에 묻혀 있다는 거죠
Right, means she was buried in
low-lying land in Dade county.
그래도 아직 범위가 너무 넓어요
Still, it's a large area.
알았네. 계속 조사해 보게, 울프
Okay, stay on it, Mr. Wolfe, stay on it.
어린 여자 애들이 드라마나
보면서 놀고 있었지
Young girls just hanging
out watching soaps,
살인자와 마주칠 줄은
전혀 모른 채 말이야
not expecting to have to confront a killer.
그런 건 아무도 모르죠
No one ever does.
18살에 삶과 죽음을 겪다니
Life and death at 18.
유감스러운 일이야
Shame.
이 핏자국은 엉뚱한 곳에 있네요
These blood stains seem out of place.
어디 가?
Where you going?
박사님, 살아 있는 사람이 있어요!
Alexx, we've got a live one!
질식사하기 직전이야
She's almost suffocated.
미라벨라 가 1818번지로
응급 구조대 출동 바랍니다
Rescue to 1818 Mirabella Street.
그 남자가... 그 남자가...
He.... he....
- 쇼크 상태에 빠지려고 해
- 괜찮아요. 괜찮아질 거예요
- She's going into shock.
- It's okay, you're gonna be okay.
존슨 씨, 부인이 실종된 날에 관해서
아드님과 얘기하고 싶습니다
Mr. Johnson, I'd like to talk to your son
about the day your wife disappeard.
우린 이미 다 진술을 했습니다
저 앤 아무것도 못 봤어요
We've been through this.
He didn't see anything.
알겠습니다만, 괜찮으시다면
I understand that,
but if it would be okay,
진술을 다 하셨는지는
제가 확인하려고 합니다
I'd like to determine that for myself.
일 년이 지난 이제 와서 왜요?
What, a year later?
존슨 씨, 이런 종류의 충격은 종종
치유되는 데 시간이 좀 걸리기도 합니다
You see, Mr. Johnson,
sometimes with a trauma like this,
it can take some time for it to dissipate.
분명히 말하지만
저 앤 아무것도 못 봤어요
I'm telling you, he didn't see anything.
- 좋습니다. 해 보죠
- 가능하면
- Fine, let's go.
- I meant alone.
저 혼자 얘기했으면 합니다
If that would be okay.
그러시죠
Yeah.
완전히 똑같단다, 애덤
It's exactly right, Adam.
작다는 거 빼곤
진짜 배지랑 완전히 똑같아
That's just like a big shield, only smaller.
만질 때 느낌이 좋아요
I like the way it feels.
자, 애덤, 그 배지에서
뭐가 특이한지 말해 보렴
Now, Adam, tell me what's
special about the gold shield.
위에 독수리가 있는 거요?
It has an eagle on top of it?
그래. 관찰력이 좋구나
It does. You see, now,
you have a good eye.
제가요? / 그렇단다
I do? / You do, son.
애덤, 이게 네게는 힘든 일이겠지만
Adam, what I wanna do,
is goint to be hard,
엄마가 실종되신 날에 대해서
몇 가지 물어보고 싶구나
but I want to ask you a few questions
about the day your mom disappeared.
날 도와줄 수 있겠니?
Could you help me with that?
그래, 좋아
Okay, good.
음, 그러니까...
Now, your mom....
엄마가 널 축구 연습에 데려다 준
다음에 무슨 일이 생겼니?
your mom drove you to soccer practice,
and then what happened?
여기 네 공
Here's your ball.
연습 잘하렴
5시에 데리러 올게
Have a good practice.
I'll see you at 5:00.
소리 지르면 머리를 날려 버릴 거야
네 어린 아들놈한테도 똑같이 해 줄 거고
Scream, and I'll blow your head off
and I'll do the same to your little boy.
앞자리에 남자가 있었어요...
I saw a guy in the front seat...
엄마에게 바짝 붙어서...
close to my mom...
속삭이고 있었어요
whispering.
앞자리에 있었다고?
He was in the front seat?
애덤, 난 네가 앞자리에
있었다고 생각했는데
Adam, I... I thought you
were in the front seat.
아니에요. 엄마는 절 앞자리에
절대 못 타게 하셨어요
No. Mom never let me sit in the front.
- 에어백 때문에요
- 에어백이라...
Air bags. / Air bags...
그래, 그 남자가 속삭이고 있었다고?
Okay, and he.. he was whispering...
어떻게 그걸 아니?
How could you tell?
무슨 말을 하는지 안 들렸거든요
Cause I couldn't hear them.
잠깐만요
Wait.
음악을 틀었어요
He turned the music up...
엄청나게 크게요
crazy loud.
제가 엄마를
지켜 드렸어야 하는데
I should have protected her.
아무것도 막지 못했어요
I didn't do anything to stop it.
애덤, 때때로 아무것도 하지 않는 게
가장 좋을 때도 있단다
Adam, sometimes the
smartest thing to do is to do nothing.
그래, 그 남자에 대해서
기억나는 건 또 없니?
Now, what else do you
remeber about him?
머리카락요
Hair.
긴 머리를 등 뒤로
늘어뜨리고 있었어요
He had long hair, down his back.
고무 밴드로 묶었고요
He tide it, with a rubber band.
그래, 그러니까...
말총머리를 했다는 거니?
Okay, you mean...
you mean like a ponytail?
말총머리라...
Like a ponytail.
애덤, 정말 잘했어
Adam, that is perfect.
이분은 몽타주 그리는 분이시란다
Now this lady is our sketch artist.
그 남자의 얼굴이 어떻게 생겼는지
잘 기억나게 도와주실 거야. 알았지?
She's gonna help you remember
What his face looks like, all right?
- 배지 고맙습니다
- 별말을 다 하는구나
- Thanks for the pin.
- You bet, partner, you bet.
시작하세요
Go a head, ma'am.
존슨 부인의 밴을 다시
조사해 봐야겠어
We need to go back to Lydia Johnson's
van and have another look.
뭘 찾으시게요?
Have another look at what?
살인자는 앞자리에 앉아 있었어
뭔가를 만졌을지도 모르지
The killer was in the front seat.
He may have touched something.
알겠습니다
All right.
먼지 알레르기가 없길 바라
Hope you're not allergic to dust.
이게 존슨 부인의 미니 밴이야
This is Lydia Johnson's mini-van.
지문을 채취하긴 힘들겠는데요
Can't print these.
열쇠 있으세요, 형사님?
You have the keys, Frank?
그래 / 고마워요
Yeah. / Thanks.
존슨 씨 아들이 음악 소리가
아주 컸다고 했죠?
Johnson's kid said the music
was crazy loud, right?
그래. 그렇다면
이 방송은 아닌 거 같군
Yeah, but not on that station.
저건 주부들이 듣는 음악이야
That's housewife music.
직접 만든 CD와 라벨이네요
Homemade CD and a homemade label.
- 부인 걸까?
- 아닐 것 같네요
- The wife's?
- No, I don't think so.
남자의 사진과 주소가 라벨에 있네요
Guy's picture's on it, his address, too.
- 포트로더데일 시군
- 예, 가 보죠
- Fort Lauderdale.
- Yeah. Let's go.
밴드의 리드 보컬인가,
아니면 솔로인가?
You the lead singer or just a solo act?
누구시죠?
Who are you?
마이애미 과학 수사대입니다
Miami CSI.
피살자의 차에서 당신이
직접 만든 CD를 찾았습니다
We found a homemade copy of your
CD in a murder victim's vehicle.
무슨 말씀하시는지 모르겠군요
I don't know what you're talking about.
그럼 리디아 존슨도 모르시겠군요
I suppose you don't know
Lydia Johnson, either.
누구요?
Who?
플로리다에서 가장 큰 미디어 기업의
소유주 제임스 존슨의 부인 말이야
Wife of the owner of Florida's
largest media conglomerate,
James Johnson.
8살 난 아들이 자기 눈앞에서
엄마가 살해되는 걸 봤지
Has an eight-year-old son who saw
somebody kill his mom right in font of him.
전 아무도 죽이지 않았어요
아시겠어요?
I didn't kill anybody, all right?
- 난 증오 범죄자가 아니라고요
- 좋습니다
I'm not hater. / Fine.
그럼 왜 그 부인의 미니 밴에
당신 CD가 있는 거죠?
What was your CD doing
inside their minivan?
존슨 씨에게 물어보지 그래요?
Why don't you ask
Mr. Johnson about the CD?
그날 아침에 존슨 씨 차에 올라타서
제 음악을 한번 들어 봐 달라고 했어요
I jumped in his car that morning.
I told him to take a listen.
그게 뭐가 대단하다는
건지 모르겠군요
I don't see what the big deal is.
당신 아내가 사라지던 날
웬 모르는 사람이
On the day that your wife disappears,
a kid that you don't know
당신 차로 뛰어들어서는
자기 노래를 들려줬다는데
forces his way into your car
and makes you listen to his song.
그게 별일이 아니라고 생각하시는군요
You don't think that's big deal.
그렇게 요행을 바라는 연예인
지망생이 어디 한둘인 줄 아세요?
You think that's the first kid to
pull a Rupert Pupkin on me?
통과. '멜로우 101' 방송에 줘 버려
청취자들이 듣다 잠들겠군
Pass. Give it to Mellow 101.
Let them put their listeners to sleep.
존슨 씨, 정말 죄송하지만
Mr. Johnson, I'm so sorry about this.
이걸 한번 들어 보셔야 해요
제목이 '플라이애미'인데, 한번 들어 보세요
You got to hear this.
This is called "Flyami". Check it out.
플라이애미, 플라이애미, 플라이애미
Flyami, Flyami, Flyami
여자들은 죽이지, 마이애미
The girls are hot, Miami
여자들이 날아다니지, 마이애미
The girls are fly, Miami
두 여자를 한 번에, 플라이애미
Two girls at once, Fyami
내 평생 들어 본 노래 중 최악이야
This is the worst song I have
ever heard in my life.
이건 내 명함이야
Here's my card.
소질이 좀 생기거든 전화해
When you get some talent,
give me a call.
에미넴처럼 되고 싶다는 애들이
한 달에 천 명이에요
1,000 of those Eminem wannbes a month.
떼어 내 버리려고
명함을 줬을 뿐입니다
Just gave him my card to get rid of him.
그럼 차 문을
잠갔어야죠, 제임스
You should have locked
your doors, James.
자동 잠금장치가
어디에 있는지 못 찾아서요
Well, I would've if I could've
found the auto lock.
아내 차였거든요
그날 아침에 차를 바꿔 탔어요
It's my wife's car.
We swapped that morning.
아내가 실종되던 날
서로 차를 바꿔 탔는데
You and your wife swapped cars
on the day she disappeared,
그게 경찰에게 알려야 할 정도로
중요하다고 생각하지 않으셨습니까?
and you didn't think it was
important to tell the police.
그게 중요한 일인지는 몰랐네요
I didn't think it was important.
그놈이 리디아의 실종과
관련이 있다고 생각하십니까?
You thinks this guy have something
to do with Lydia's disappearance?
제가 알 턱이 있겠습니까?
I mean, how could I possibly know?
일 년이나 지나서야
이 사실을 알았는데 말입니다
I mean, I'm getting this
information a year later.
뭔가 더 알아내시면
When you find out more,
- 전화 주십시오
- 명함은 있습니다, 제임스
- give me a call.
- I have your card, James.
그렇지만 감사합니다
But, thank you.
제임스의 재정 기록을
다시 한번 살펴보자고
Let's go back into his
financial records, please.
이미 했어. 일 년 전에
Did. A year ago.
한 번 더 해 보지
Let's do it agian.
킴벌리, 여학생 클럽에
침입한 남자가 이 사람이에요?
Kimberly, the man who broke into
your sorority house, did he look like this?
이름이 헨리 데리어스예요
His name is Henry Darius.
맞아요
Yes.
무슨 일이 일어났는지 말해 줄래요?
Can you tell me what happened?
어, 제가 마상 시합 버스를 놓쳤어요
Um, I missed the tournament bus.
집에 들어갔을 때, 어...
When I walked into the house and, um...
온통 피투성이였어요
there was blood everywhere.
여자 애들은 바닥에 쓰러져 있었고...
The girls were still on the floor, and...
캐이티는 여전히
신음 소리를 내고 있었죠
Katie was still moaning.
그 남자의 등 바로 뒤로
까치발을 하고 걸었어요
I tiptoed right past his back.
세탁실에 숨은 건
정말 잘한 일이에요
You did good to hide in the laundry room.
그 남자가 무슨 말 없었나요?
누구와 얘기하지는 않았어요?
Did he say anything?
Did he talk to anyone?
어... "알렉사 어디 있어?
어디 있느냐고?" 하더라고요
Uh.. "Where's Alexa? Where is she?"
알렉사가 누구예요?
Who is Alexa?
알렉사 엔더콧요
3학년 언니예요
Alexa Endecott.
Third year sister.
계속 알렉사가 어디 있는지 물었어요
He kept asking where she was.
알렉사도 다른 사람들과 함께
포트로더데일 시에 있나요?
Is she in Fort Lauderdale with the others?
아니요
No.
알렉사는 마상 시합을
몰래 빼먹었어요
I know she was ditching the tournament,
뭣 때문에 그랬는지는 모르겠어요
but I can't remember what for.
킴벌리, 잘 생각해 봐요
Okay, Kimberly, I need you to think.
알렉사가 어디 있는지 기억해 봐요
I need you to remember where she is.
코코 승마 클럽이에요
Coco Riding Club.
오늘 아침 11시에 갔대요
She went around 11:00 a.m.
this morning.
어디인지 알아, 캘리
고맙네
I know where that is, Calleigh.
Thank you.
- 케인 반장님
- 맥 테일러 반장님
- Lieutenant Caine.
- Detective Mac Tayler.
조금 늦었군요
Could've used a tailwind.
괜찮습니다
No worries.
데리어스가 벌써 여학생 클럽에
침입했다고 들었습니다
Heard Darius had already
hit a sorority house.
그래요, 마이애미 대학입니다
특정인을 찾고 있더군요, 맥
Yes, Miami University.
He's looking for somebody specific, Mc.
- 이름을 알아냈나요?
- 알렉사 엔더콧, 21살입니다
- Have a name?
- Alexa Endecott, 21.
이제 휴대 전화도 안 됩니다
No longer using her cell phone.
- 어디 있는지 아십니까?
- 예, 그래요
- We know where she is?
- We do.
나쁜 소식은 데리어스도
알고 있다는 겁니다, 맥
The bad news, Mac, so does he.
어서 갑시다
Come on.
클럽 소유지에 왜 6명이나 되는 경관이
함부로 들어왔는지 설명해 주십시오
Please explain why I just had six
police officers barge to club property.
살인 사건 조사 때문입니다
It's called a murder investigation.
- 농담이시죠?
- 뉴욕에서 온 탈주자입니다
- You're kidding, right?
- He's a fugitive from New York.
마이애미에서 마구잡이로
살인을 저지르고 있어요
He's on a killing spree in Miami.
알렉사 엔더콧을 노리고 있습니다
여기 있습니까?
He's targeting Alexa Endecott.
Is she here?
아까는 저 아래에서
장애물 넘기를 하고 있었습니다
Uh, she was jumping
steeples earlier, down that way.
감사합니다
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa.
말이 겁을 좀 먹었는데요
He's a little spooked.
A.E.
알렉사 엔더콧이군요
이걸 한번 봐요, 맥
Alexa Endecott.
Take a look at this, Mac.
- 피군요
- 아직 마르지도 않았고요
Blood. / Still wet, too.
알렉사의 피예요
That blood is Alexa's.
반장님
Lieutenant.
그래
Yeah.
뭔가 찾았습니다
We found something.
응급 구조대가 오고 있습니다
Rescue's on its way.
이 클럽의 경비원입니다
He's security for the club.
괜찮으십니까?
무슨 일이 있었죠?
Sir, you okay?
What happened?
저희는 알렉사 엔더콧을
찾고 있습니다
We're looking for Alexa Endecott.
그 남자가 제 차를 가져갔어요
Guy took my car.
알겠습니다
Okay.
총은 어디 있죠?
Where's your gun?
그 남자가 가져갔어요
He.. he took it.
맥
Mac.
긴급 상황이다
Yeah, I've got a police emergency.
코코 승마 클럽 소속 경비 차량에
무선 연결을 해라
Connect me to the security car
assigned to the Coco Riding Club.
과거 행동 방식으로 봐서는 기회가
되는대로 바로 차를 버릴 겁니다
Based on past behavior, he'll ditch
the car first chance he gets.
시간이 별로 없어요
We don't have much time.
- 그래요
- 지금 연결하고 있습니다
- Yeah.
- We're connecting you right now.
맥, 당신보다 데리어스를
잘 아는 사람은 없어요
Nobody knows him better
than you do, Mac.
경비입니다
Security.
헨리 데리어스?
Henry Darius?
맥 테일러 반장님, 멀리 뉴욕에서
여기까지 오셨군요
Detective Mac Taylor, all the
way from New York City.
그 간호사들의 아파트 양탄자에서
피 한 방울이라도 찾았나요?
Hey, those nurses' apartment, did
you ever get the blood out of the carpet.
여기 마이애미 데이드 경찰
호레이시오 케인 반장님과 함께 있네
I'm here with Lieutenant
Horatio Caine, Miami-Dade P.D.
지원 요청을 하셨군요
이거 영광이네요
You had to call for backup.
I'm flattered.
데리어스, 알렉사와 지금 당장
얘기하고 싶네
Darius, I want to speak
to Alexa right now.
지금 말할 수 있는
상황이 아니라서요
She can't talk right now.
도로를 이미 봉쇄했고
모두 자네를 찾고 있네
I've got road blocks and all of
Miami's looking for you, my friend.
뭐, 다 예상했던 겁니다
Well, I would expect no less.
자동차에는 GPS가 장착되어 있네
우린 자넬 찾아낼 거야
Car has GPS, we'll find you.
내가 찾게 놔둬야
날 찾을 수 있을 겁니다
You will find me when
I want you to find me.
알렉사 엔더콧이라
그 엔더콧 가문인가요?
Alexa Endecott, the Endecotts?
사탕수수 가공과 철도 건설을 하는
그 엔더콧 가문 맞습니다
The Endecotts.
Sugar cane and railways.
미국의 모든 대도시에서
자선 사업을 하죠
Philanthropy in every
big city in America.
아주 부잣집 여자 애를 골랐군요
He picked a very rich girl.
반장님
Lieutenant.
GPS를 차에서 떼어서 버렸습니다
GPS kicked out the vehicle.
경관
Officer.
뭐 만진 거 있나?
Did you touch anything else?
아닙니다
트렁크만 열었습니다, 반장님
No. Just popped the trunk, sir.
차엔 아무도 없습니다
Car's empty.
- 우리가 살펴보겠네
- 예, 그러십시오
- We're gonna have a look.
- Sure thing.
데리어스가 무전기는 부쉈지만
감시 카메라는 그대로 뒀군요
Darius disabled the radio,
but not the video camera.
디지털 방식이라
안에 테이프가 없어요
It's a projected image, no tape inside.
경비 회사에 연락해서
뭐가 찍혔는지 보죠
I'll call the security company,
see what they have.
다른 게 있군요
Something else.
뭘 찾았나요?
Do you get something?
"6601-C6"
지도의 좌표처럼 들리는군요
Sounds like it could be map coordinates.
자기가 갈 곳을 알리다니
데리어스답지 않은데요
It's not like him to telegraph
where he's going.
전에 들렀던 곳일 수도 있죠, 맥
Maybe it's where he's been, Mac.
존슨 부인이 묻혀 있는 곳이겠군요
Burial site for your Lydia Johnson.
제 생각도 그렇습니다
That's what I'm thinking.
감시 카메라 영상을 얻어 올게요
Why don't I'm gonna get security video.
필요하면 경관을
한 명 데려가세요
Take one of my officers,
if you need one.
그래, 에릭
좌표의 위치를 알아봐 주게
Yeah, Eric.
Run some coordinates, please.
6601-C6
6601-C6.
어디인가?
Talk to me.
플로리다 주 지도첩 같네요
Looks like a Florida street guide.
데이드 카운티의 이름이
있는 자리와 정확히 일치해요
Page definitely corresponds to
a location in Dade County.
삽에서 나온
흙 성분을 고려해 봤을 때
Yeah, factoring in the soil
evidence from the shovel,
홈스테드 시의
습지대를 가리키는 것 같아요
he's pointing us to a
wetlands area in Homestead.
알겠네. 거기서 보도록 하지
All right, I'll meet you there.
땅 아래를 스캔하고 있군요
Underground scanning.
이거 어느 군부대에서
가져오신 거예요?
What branch of the military
did we get this from?
아직 완성된 기술은 아니지만
우리 목표물을 찾아줄 거야
Technology's not perfected,
but it'll get us there.
무슨 소리를 찾고 있는데요?
What are they listening for?
존슨 부인의 롤렉스 시계는
가짜야, 에릭
Lydia Johnson's Rolex is a fake, Eric.
초침이 부드럽게 움직이는 게 아니라
딸각딸각 소리가 나겠군요
Meaning it ticks instead of sweeps.
남편이 인색한 게 도움이 됐네요
Good thing her husband was cheap.
배터리가 아직 남아 있기만을
빌어 보자고
Let's just hope, the battery holds up.
뭔가 찾았네요
He found something.
좋아
Good.
알렉스, 옷과 보석이
존슨 부인과 맞아떨어져
Alexx? The clothes and the jewelry
are match to Lydia Johnson.
확실히 하기 위해
치과 기록을 살펴볼게
I'll take dental records to be sure.
가족이 일 년을 기다렸어
The family has waited a year.
그래, 빨리할게
I'm on it.
호레이시오
Horatio....
명함이야
a business card.
뭔가 더 알아내시면...
When you find out more...
전화 주십시오
give me a call.
남편의 명함이군
It's the husband's business card.
존슨 부인의 살인범을
지목하는 것일 수도 있겠군요
Maybe Lydia's pointing us to her killer.
제임스, 부인의 시신에서
당신 명함을 발견했어요
James, we found your business
card on your wife's body.
제 아내니까 당연하죠
She is my wife.
죽었지만
Was.
아내를 찾아 주셔서 감사합니다
I'm just glad you found her.
예, 틀림없이 그럴 테죠
I'm yeah, I bet you are.
무슨 의미로 하신 말씀이죠?
What is that supposed to mean?
부인에게 5백만 달러의
생명 보험을 들었더군요
You took out a $5 million life
insurance policy on your wife.
보험사 약관상 부인의 시체를
확인하기 전에는, 한 푼도 받지 못하죠
The way the policy is designed,
you don't get a penny until
you produce her body.
일 년 내내 보험사에
매주 전화를 했더군요, 제임스
You also called the department
every week for a year, james.
가족의 재정 계획을
세우느라 그랬습니다
Family fiscal planning.
그뿐이에요
Nothing more.
그 보험은 아들이
태어난 주에 가입한 겁니다
Took the policy out the
week our son was born.
부인의 시신에서
당신의 명함을 찾았다는 걸
Need I remind you that
I found your business card
다시 상기시켜 드려야 합니까?
on your dead wife's body?
반으로 접혀 있는 상태로요
Folded in half.
원래 제가 그렇게 해서 줍니다
That's how I hand them out.
누군가에게 줬는데 그 사람이
아내에게 줬을 겁니다
Must have given it to
somebody who gave it to her.
누구에게요?
누구에게 줬습니까?
To who?
Who would that be?
말씀드렸다시피, 전 일주일에
수백 명의 사람을 만납니다
I told you.
I meet hundreds of people a week,
누구라도 그럴 수 있죠
it could be anyone.
명함에 찍힌 지문의
조회 결과가 나왔습니다
ID's the print on the card.
고맙네, 에릭
Thank you, Eric.
음, 제임스...
Well, James...
가만히 앉아 있어요
sit tight.
점점 재미있어지려고 하니까요
It's about to get interesting.
브라이언, 이제 널 살인으로
기소할 증거가 충분히 있어
Brian, right now I have enough
to charge you with murder.
전 존슨 부인을 죽이지 않았어요
I did not kill that lady.
그럼 존슨 부인의 시체에서
나온 명함에
Then explain to me
how your fingerprint got
왜 자네 지문이 찍혀 있는지
설명해 보게
on the business card
in Lydia Johnson's grave
맙소사, 전... 전...
My God, I... I...
전 일이 이렇게
엉망이 될 줄 몰랐어요
I don't know how this
got so screwed up.
도움이 필요한가?
You want some help with it?
존슨 씨를 몇 주 동안 따라다녔어요
I follwed Mr. Johnson for weeks.
존슨 씨의 자동차 생김새나
스케줄, 모든 걸 알아냈죠
I had his car information,
his schedule, everything about him.
그런데 존슨 씨는 자네 음악을
들어 보려고도 하지 않았지
And then he refused to
help with your music.
제가 전혀 재능이 없는
것처럼 대했어요
He treated me like I was a no-talent.
그래서 다음 계획을 실행했어요
So I went to Plan B.
다음 계획이 뭐였지, 브라이언?
What was "Plan B", Brian?
다른 사람을 고용해서
존슨 씨를 겁주는 거였어요
I hired someone to scare him.
겁만 주는 거였어요
Scare him.
그 사람에게 존슨 씨 명함과 주소를 주고
점심 이후에 행동하라고 했어요
I gave him his card, his address,
I told him to get him after lunch.
존슨 씨는 매일 스케줄이 같았거든요
He had the same schedule
every day, Johnson had.
그날 자기 아내와 차를 바꿔 탄 것만
제외하고 말이지
Except for the day that
he swapped cars with his wife.
그 얼간이가 저한테
That moron told me
"아내도 남편만큼
맘에 들던데"라고 했어요
"The wife's just as good as the husband."
연습 잘하렴
5시에 데리러 올게
Have a good practice.
I'll see you at five.
그때 봐요 / 그래
See you. / Okay.
소리 지르면 머리를 날려 버릴 거야
네 어린 아들놈한테도 똑같이 해줄 거고
Scream and I'll blow your head off,
and I'll do the same to your little boy.
존슨 씨를 겁주려면
아내를 겁줘도 되죠
You know, scare her to scare him.
그 자식은 어쩌다가 사고로
부인을 쏴 버렸다고 했어요
Only he tells me, he
accidentally shot her.
사고랬어요
Accidentally.
운전해
Drive.
제발요
Please.
그런데 이제까지 아무에게도
말하지 않았단 말인가, 브라이언?
And all this time, Brian,
you told no one?
겁이 났어요
I was afraid.
중죄 모살에 대해서 알아요
제가 죽인 거랑 똑같이 취급하잖아요
I know about felony murder..
It's like I killed her myself, right?
그래, 아주 정확히 알고 있군
Yeah, that's exactly right my friend.
법을 잘 아는군
You do know the law.
브라이언...
Brian...
이 사람이 자네가 고용한 사람인가?
이름이 헨리 데리어스네
Is that the man that you hired?
His name is Henry Darius.
아니에요
No.
그럼 누구를 고용했나?
Who did you hire then?
'로지'라는 이름밖에 몰라요
I only know him as "Rosie."
이메일 주소는 아는데
I have his Internet address but
존슨 부인이 실종되던 날
없앴더군요
it was canceled the
day she disappeared.
자네도 그렇게 자취라도 감추지 그랬나
이 정신 나간 친구야
That should have been the
tip off for you, my friend.
데려가게
Hook him up, please.
실례하지
Excuse me.
프랭크
Frank.
데리어스는?
Darius.
맥이 경비 회사에서 받은
비디오를 분석하고 있어
Mac's chasing down video
from the security guard.
그래, 뭔가 알아내면 알려 주게
Okay, you hear anything let me know.
저 멍청이는 어떻게 엮인 거래?
How's that loser fit in?
로지라는 놈을 고용했다는군
That loser hired somebody named Rosie,
아마 데리어스를 아는 놈일 거야
who probably knows Darius.
어떻게?
How?
좋은 질문이네, 프랭크
That is a good question, Frank.
존슨 부인에게 가 있을 테니
필요하면 그리로 연락하게
You need me, I'll be with
Lydia Johnson, all right?
그래
All right.
시체가 손상되지 않았어
옷에 싸여서 그대로 있었지
The body's intact.
Held together by her clothing.
엉망이지만 이거 하나는 알아냈어
They're a mass,
but I did notice one thing.
총을 맞았군
She was shot.
블라우스 옆과 옆구리에
총알 구멍이 있어
Hole in the clothes on the
side of the blouse, and her waist.
견갑골에서 총알을 추출했어
Projectile recovered from her scapula.
각도가 이상한데, 알렉스
That's an odd angle, Alexx.
오른쪽에서 왼쪽으로
앞에서 뒤로야
Right to left.
Front to back.
사고였을 수도 있을까?
Could it have been an accident?
이건 아냐
Not this one.
오른쪽 관자놀이에 이건...
Right in the temple...
오른쪽 관자놀이라...
그건 처형 방식이지
Right in the temple...
that's an execution.
머리에 쏘면 얼마나 피가
많이 나오는지 알지?
You know how much
head shots bleed.
그래. 밴에 있던 피의
흩뿌려진 모양이 설명되는군
Right, so that explains the
blood spatter in the van, doesn't it?
제발 살려 주세요
전 아이가 있어요
Oh, please God.
I have a baby!
왜 모두 데리어스의 얘기에
속아 넘어갔는지 알겠어
Now it makes sense why
everyone bought Darius' story.
피의 양이 데리어스의 범행 수법과
일치하는 것만 보고 넘어간 거야
Just by the volume of blood fits his MO.
데리어스가 아니었어
So it wasn't Darius.
존슨 부인을 죽이고 삽을
무덤에 가져다 둔 건 로지야
It was Rosie who killed her
and left the shovel in the grave.
호레이시오
Horatio.
진짜 범인에 대한 단서를
잡았길 바랄게
I hope you've got a
lead on the real killer.
여기 있구나
There he is.
엄마를 찾아 주셔서 감사해요
Thanks for finding my mom.
네 도움이 있어서 가능했단다, 애덤
Well, I did it with your help, Adam.
말총머리를 한 남자는 찾으셨어요?
Did you find the ponytail man?
아직 못 찾았지만 꼭 찾을 거란다
I haven't found him yet, but I will.
이렇게 할 거야
And I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
내가 그놈을 찾으면
네게 제일 먼저 전화해 줄게
As soon as I find him,
I'm going to call you first.
알았지?
All right?
그럼 됐지?
So we got a deal?
그래
Okay.
꼭 그렇게 하마
We got a deal.
운전사를 죽이고
차를 바꿔 탔어요
He switched cars,
killed the driver to get the car.
응급 구조대가 지금 가고 있어요
Rescue's out and rolling.
트립 형사님이 우리가 일러 드린
번호판을 찾고 계세요
Tripp's running the plates as we speak.
멈춰 봐요
Stop the video.
뒤로 다시 감아 봐요
Rewind that, please.
데리어스의 입술이 움직였어요
뭔가를 말했어요
I saw his lips move.
He said something.
그러네요
Yeah.
- "생일 축하해"
- 생일인 걸 어떻게 알았죠?
- "Happy Birthday"
- How did he know that?
검은색 엔텍 모자를 쓰고 있군요
He's wearing a black Entek cap.
저 모자를 일부러 가져갔다면
If he took it with him,
그걸 위장용으로 사용했을 거예요
he could wear it for disguise.
마이애미 경찰에게 알릴게요
I'm going to let Miami P.D. know.
이 도로는 95번 고속도로와 만나요
You know, this road intersects with I-95.
네 시간이 지났으니
어디든 갈 수 있겠군요
It was over four hours ago,
he could be anwhere by now.
얼마나 멀리 갔을 거라고 생각하세요?
How far do you think he got?
그건 내가 알 것 같은데
I may have the answer to that.
알렉사가 방금 집 전화 응답기에
메시지를 남겼어
Alexa Endecott just left a
message on our home machine.
누가 들을지 모르겠지만, 전 알렉사예요
누가 절 납치했어요
Anyone, it's Alexa, I've
been taken by some guy.
그 남자는 갈색 머리예요
그 남자가 오기 전에 끊어야겠어요
He's got, uh, brown hair...
Got to go before he comes.
전화기도 끌게요
I'm shutting my phone off.
잠깐만. 다시 한 번 틀어 봐
Wait a second, play that again.
'남자'라고 한 다음에
무슨 소리가 들렸어
There was a sound after she said "guy".
무슨 경적 소리 같네요
Sound like a horn.
누가 절 납치...
그 남자는 갈색 머리에...
...taken by some guy....
he's got uh, brown hair...
그 남자는 갈색 머리에...
He's got, uh, brown hair...,
저 소린 한 번을 들어도
천 번을 들은 거나 다름없어요
If I've heard that sound once,
I've heard it a thousand times.
호레이시오 반장님도
예전에 맨해튼에서 일하신 적 있죠
Horatio, you worked Manhattan.
도시를 드나들 때
출발과 도착을 알리는 소리예요
Sounds and arrivals and
departures in and out of the city.
스태튼 섬까지 다니는
페리선(船)이로군요
That's the Staten Island Ferry.
이미 뉴욕에 가 있어요
They're already in New York.
어떻게 그렇게 빨리 뉴욕에
갈 수 있었을까요?
Question is how'd
they get there so fast?
니벤스 씨?
Ms. Nivens?
돌아서 주세요
Turn around, please, Ma'am.
당신에겐 G4 비행기가 있죠. 그렇죠?
You have a G-4, don't you?
그래서요? / 좀 전에 데리어스가 타고
날아가 버린 비행기죠
Why? / That is the plane
that Darius just flew away on.
그래요. 당신 때문에 그 사람이
절 두고 떠났다고요
Yes. And he left me
here because of you.
데리어스를 당신 개인 비행기에 태워서
뉴욕으로 보내 줬다고요?
You let him take your
private plane to New York?
더 어린 여자랑요
아닌 게 더 이상하겠지만요
With a younger woman,
if that doesn't that beat all.
그 여자는 인질입니다
That younger woman is a hostage.
왜 뉴욕입니까?
Why New York?
몰라요. 거기서 무슨
볼일이 있다고 했어요
I don't know. He said he had
some kind of business there.
어떤 볼일 말입니까?
What kind of business?
모든 일을 바로잡으려고
He told me he was
going to New York City
뉴욕에 간다고 했어요
to make things right.
번역수정
김난주(nanjidoo@nate.com)
한글수정
임재영(dreamimage@nate.com)
자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/clubcsi)
[CSI NY 2x07에서 계속 됩니다]